第一季 第一集
沃特出品
"你无法杀死一个看不见的人"
《隐形人之隐形特攻队二》即将上映
音频算法系统
音高清多媒体接口线
比利·乔尔 美国著名歌手、钢琴演奏家、作曲作词家
得梅因 爱荷华州
火车头深表哀悼
电影 讲述一位叫“Steele”潇洒，智慧而且浪漫的侦探。
这位神探总是和他的助手Laura在不经意的情况下侦破了一件又一件的案子。
沃特国际公司
2019年度股东大会
火车头
深水主
隐形人
玄色
梅芙女王
爱国者
极速子弹啤酒
火车头麦片
WorldView-4卫星是DigitalGlobe商用高分辨率遥感卫星
外国的淘宝
纽约一家知名餐厅
联邦调查局
自由女神像
华纳兄弟公司动作片
沃特大厦
联邦生命线 美国政府的惠民项目
星光
她和我们一样
电影《黑客帝国》里著名情节 主角面临选择
若选择蓝色药丸则回到自己的生活 红色则进入另一个世界
音像店
- Barracuda
你在杂草里潜伏的那么深
You lying so low into the weeds ♪
我打赌你是想要埋伏我
I bet you gonna ambush me ♪
你让我屈服
You'd have me down, down, down ♪
双膝着地
Down on my knees... ♪
我做了件坏事
I did a bad, bad thing ♪
I did a bad, bad thing. ♪
我做了件坏事
你全身心地祈祷
You ever pray with all your heart and soul ♪
却只换来她的决绝
Just to watch her walk away? Yeah... ♪
伦敦的呼唤着远方的小镇
London calling to the faraway towns ♪
现在战争已经开始
Now war is declared ♪
火药味越来越浓
And battle come down ♪
伦敦在召唤着地狱的冤魂
London calling to the underworld ♪
从壁橱里爬出来吧 你们这些见不得光的家伙
Come out of the cupboard, you boys and girls ♪
伦敦...
London... ♪
旅人啊...
Oh, the passenger... ♪
嘿 我超期待《隐形特攻队二》
Yo, I am so psyched for Invisible Force 2.
拜托 《隐形特攻队一》可烂了
Please. Invisible Force 1 was lame.
我最喜欢起潮人
I'm all about Rising Tide.
起潮人 深水主
Rising Tide? The Deep?
隐形人能打爆深水主
Translucent could kick The Deep's ass.
怎么可能 他是能隐身 但这就是他唯一的本事了
How? He's invisible. That's, like, all he's got. That's it.
对啊 他可以悄悄地靠近深水主
Exactly. He sneaks up on The Deep,
然后嘭 见鬼去吧
and then boom, motherfucker!
- 弟弟坐下 - 直到深水主让条鲨鱼咬掉隐形人的屌
- Sit down. - Until The Deep makes a shark bite Translucent's dick off.
深水主要怎么找到他的屌 它可是隐形的
How's he gonna find his dick? It's invisible.
我的天
Holy shit.
班吉
Benjy!
起来 起来 起来
Get up. Get up, get up, get up.
快点 班吉 快
Come on, Benjy. Come on, come on.
别过来
Stay back.
他妈的给我退后
Just stay the fuck back.
你在笑什么
What are you smiling at?
爱国者
Homelander?
你们没事吧
You boys okay?
我能 我能和你自拍一张吗
Can I... can I get a selfie?
当然可以
Course you can.
七巨头中的梅芙女王和爱国者
The Seven's Queen Maeve and Homelander
今天再次英勇地救助了人民
made another heroic save today,
他们在布鲁克林的街头
stopping a hijacked armored truck
阻止了一辆被劫持的装甲卡车
on the streets of Brooklyn,
然后留下来和一些非常幸运的粉丝
then staying behind for a photo op
- 一起合影 - 很高兴遇见你
- with some very lucky fans. - Nice to meet you.
- 琴 - 谢谢詹妮弗 现在
- Jean? - Thanks, Jennifer. And now...
所以这东西算是包含了全部的功能
So, this is pretty much everything in one.
这款蓝牙音响
Bluetooth speakers.
是立体声的 所以你可以把它放在客厅的任何地方
It's in stereo, so you can put it all around your living room,
用它找点乐子
have some fun with it.
你说过你有的是标准机顶盒 是吗
You said you have a standard cable box, right?
行 那我得给你拿个音频发射机
Okay, then I need to get you an audio transmitter,
APTX低延时
aptx low latency.
这样就能少点音频延迟
It makes it so there's less audio lag,
它还有个标准光纤
and it's got a standard optical in.
然后给你找个千兆字节HDMI
And let's hook you up with thousand-Meg hdmi.
就拿这个吧
Let's go with this one.
它是贵点
Uh, it costs a little bit more,
但是它的碳纤维的传导性强多了
but the carbon's way more conductive.
嘿 盖里
Hey, Gary. Um...
- 我真的很需要和你谈件事 - 待会儿吧 小鬼
- I really need to talk to you about something. - Later, kid.
行 好
Okay. Cool.
待会 你是说 30分钟后吗
Later... you want, like... Want, like, 30-30 minutes?
或者是45分钟后
Like, a solid 45?
打扰一下 先生
Excuse me, sir?
你好 我希望能预约一下
Hi. I'd like to make an appointment
你上门服务
for you to come over and...
安装些电缆
lay some cable.
好的 罗宾
Okay. Uh... oh, Robin.
亲爱的 亲爱的 罗宾
Oh, dear, dear, Robin.
那句话的意思可不是你想的那样
Um, that doesn't mean what you think it means.
"安装电缆"代表滚床单
Um, "Laying cable" means sex.
不 "安装管道"才代表滚床单
No, "Laying pipe" means sex.
"安装电缆"代表你想让我去你家
"Laying cable" means you want me to come over to your house
拉泡陈年老屎
and just take a big, old shit.
- 那真恶心 - 行吧
- That's disgusting. - Well, okay.
但是 但这可是你刚说的
But you... Who-who said it, though?
行了 你准备好了吗 虽然你尽了努力
Okay. Are you ready? Despite your best efforts,
我还是很饿
I'm actually still hungry.
我其实变得更饿了
I'm actually more hungry now.
- 我们可是刚聊骚完 要去哪里 - 我不知道
- Where are we gonna go after all this hot talk? - I don't know.
- 你懂的 - 更重要的是 我们之后要去哪儿
- You know? - More importantly, where are we gonna go
"安装些电缆"
to lay some cable afterwards?
真是的
Geez.
所以 你有问他了吗
So, did you ask him?
- 问谁 - 盖里
- Who? - Gary.
你有没有向盖里要求加薪
Did you ask Gary for the raise?
对 对 怎么说呢
Yeah. Yeah. It was... It was a...
今天像是一团乱麻 而且他超级忙
Look, it was a crazy day, and-and he was super busy,
但明天我一定问 对
but tomorrow for sure. Yes.
行吧
Okay.
我应该要怎么做 去踹他家门吗
What was I supposed to do, kick his door down?
像爱国者那样
Like Homelander?
我说了 "行吧"
I said "Okay."
是 但你不是真心的
Yeah, but you didn't mean it.
我看到你的表情了
Hey, I see the look.
我看到了 别这样
I see it. Come on.
这就像我们刚开始约会的时候
This is like when we started dating.
我不觉得那是 我不觉得那是真的
I don't think that's... I don't think that's true.
老哥 最后还是我约你出去的
Dude, I had to ask you out.
原谅我想要等一等
Well, excuse me for waiting.
你没听说过骑士精神吗
You ever hear of chivalry?
听好了 这是关于你得到你应得的东西
Listen, this is about you getting what you deserve.
我还在学校忍受折磨
I'm killing myself at school
因为我觉得这对我们两个都是值得的
because I think it's gonna be worth it for both of us.
你懂的 如果我们开始同居的话
You know, if we move in together.
等等 什么 什么 等等
Wait, what? What? W-w-wait. Hey, hey, hey.
嘿 你说什么
Hey, hey. What was that?
你刚刚说什么
What'd you just say?
我是说 我们不能一直在你爸爸那里
Well, I mean, we can't keep, you know, laying pipe
滚床单啊
at your dad's place.
尽力一声不响
Trying to be all quiet.
看着那个蠢蠢的比利·乔尔
Staring up at that dumb Billy Joel post...
- 海报 - 嘿
- Poster. - Hey.
你可不准小瞧比利·乔
Don't you ever besmirch Billy Jo...
我停不下来 我停不下来 我停不下来了
I can't stop. I can't stop. I can't stop. I can't stop.
不能停 停不下来
Can't stop. Can't stop.
罗宾
Robin?
Robin!
罗宾
让力量穿透墙壁
Let the energy go through the wall.
我是星光
I am Starlight.
我重50公斤 高一米七
I'm 110 pounds, and I'm five foot six.
请转一圈
Turn around, please.
好的 让我们看看吧 亲爱的
Okay. Let's see it, dear.
你应该移开视线
You should look away.
- 抱歉 - 你应该把视线从摄像机上移开
- Sorry? - You should turn away from the camera,
并且闭上眼睛 不然我会亮瞎你的
and you should close your eyes, or else I'll blind you.
好的
All right.
好了 开始吧
Okay, go ahead.
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我生下来就有超能力
I was born super-abled.
我妈妈非常的兴奋
Uh, my mom was thrilled.
她带我参加了所有的女性英雄选美比赛
She took me to all the little Miss Hero pageants,
但是我讨厌极了
but I hated it.
我现在还能
Ugh, I mean, I can still...
闻到那种发胶味
Smell the hairspray.
但是
Uh, but...
问答环节的时候 他们总是问我的愿望是什么
At the Q and A, they always asked me what my wish was,
我每次都回答 "拯救世界"
and I always said, "To save the world."
然后裁判们就咯咯笑起来 就像
And the judges just chuckled like
我说了什么可爱的话 但是
it was cute. But...
那对我来说不是玩笑
it wasn't a joke to me.
从什么时候开始 "心怀希望"和"幼稚"
Since when did "Hopeful" And "Naive"
成了同样的东西
become the same thing?
我是说 如果你不是为了拯救世界
I mean, why would you get into this business
那为什么要投身于这个行业呢
if not to save the world?
这是我的毕生所愿
That's all I have ever wanted.
所以我一直都希望能成为
And that's why I've always wanted
七巨头的一员
to be in the Seven.
谢谢你 詹妮弗
Thanks, Jennifer.
罗宾的葬礼挺好的
Thought Robin's service was nice.
你看到有多少人来了吗
Did you see how many people came?
大家都很尊敬她
Lot of respect for that girl.
那屋子里可是满怀爱意
Lot of love in the room.
而且布道 布道也很不错
And the spread. What a spread.
真的是很好
Just really nice.
那完全无法传达
That does not begin to convey
真是的 也许其他台有电影在播
Aw, geez. Maybe there's a movie on.
- 我们可以换台 - 别换 就看这个
- No, we can switch it. - No, keep it. Keep it.
真是一场遗憾的悲剧
Awful, tragic loss.
我向罗宾·沃德的家人表达深切的哀悼
My deepest condolences to Robin Ward's family.
我当时正在追逐银行劫匪
I was chasing these bank robbers.
此时她很不巧地走在马路中间
She just stepped in the middle of the street,
而我 我没办法...
and I-I couldn't...
路中间...
Middle of the...
她明明离人行道只有半步远
She was a half step off the fucking curb.
别这样 休伊
Oh, now, come on, Hughie.
别生气 好吗
Just, uh, don't get upset, okay? Just...
他自己心里知道
He knows.
沃特公司的每个人都...
Everyone at Vought is just...
为罗宾感到难过
just wrecked about Robin.
但是听着 你俩还没有结婚
Now, you two weren't married, and look,
严格来说 你并没有索赔权
technically, there's no legal claim.
但是沃特公司想做正确的事
But Vought wants to do the right thing:
那就是为你提供四万五千美元的赔偿
Offer you $45,000 in restitution.
你只需要在这里
All you have to do is sign
签字就行了
right here,
然后我把支票给你
and I'll offer you the check.
这是一份保密协议
This is a confidentiality agreement.
只是一个常规条款
It's a boilerplate nda.
我签了这个 然后
I sign this, and...
我就再也不能说起这件事了
I can't talk about it?
就得假装无事发生吗
Have to pretend like it didn't happen,
就好像我从未握着罗宾的断手一样
like I wasn't holding Robin's arms in my hands?
听着 我知道你很生气
Look, I know you're upset,
但我们只是想帮忙
but we're just trying to help.
那你们倒是说你们很抱歉啊
Then say you're sorry.
什么
Excuse me?
你们这些人表面上说 "我们的哀悼"
I mean, you people say "Our condolences"
"我很同情" 或是 "我们很遗憾"
and "My sympathies" And "Our regrets,"
但没有一个人敢看着我的双眼
but nobody can look me in the fucking eye
对我说"抱歉"
and say "I'm sorry."
我什么都不会签的 给我滚出去
I'm not signing anything. Get out.
我说 你给我滚出去
I said get the hell out!
你还好吗
You okay?
如我所说 这真的只是个常规条款
As I said, boilerplate nda, really.
流程化的东西而已
Pretty standard stuff.
我能考虑一下吗
Can I think about it?
如果你有任何疑问 就...
If you have any questions at all, just, uh...
44编队 代号20
Unit 44, code 20.
地址是142063路
Address is 142063rd street...
有疯子在外面闹事吗
Any maniacs out there?
没有 平静的夜晚
Mm-mm. Quiet night.
夜夜皆是如此
Like every night.
太倒霉了
That's too bad.
我们真的急需炒作的机会
We could really use the press right now.
安妮
Oh, Annie.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
别担心 我拿不到那个工作的
Don't worry. I didn't get the job.
那可不一定
You don't know that.
他们在全国面试女孩
They're auditioning girls nationwide.
估计是女伯爵被录用了
Besides, Countess probably got it.
她的面试表现很好
She's so good in a room.
如果你消极的话 消极的事便会发生
If you're negative, negative things happen to you.
您好
Hello?
是的 我是她妈妈
Yes, I'm her mother.
好的
Uh, yes. Uh...
请稍等
Uh, one moment.
是他们
It's them.
您好
Hello?
是的 我就是
Yes, this is she.
我被录用了
I got it?
你被录用了 你被录用了
You got it! You got it!
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
对不起 对不起
Uh, I'm so... I'm so sorry.
刚才信号不好
It's a weird connection.
我也不知道发生了什么
I don't know what that was, actually.
妈的
Oh, shit.
是吗
Yeah?
我认为她在吸毒
I think she was an addict.
有针孔吗
Needle tracks?
一只胳膊上有12个针孔
12 marks on one arm.
源源不断的毒品被运入
More dope coming in.
源源不断的毒贩开始工作
More pushers at work.
你在干嘛
What you doing?
我不能以刑事案件起诉火车头
Can't file a criminal case against A-train
超级英雄就像警察一样
Supes are like cops.
他们受法律保护
They can't be charged
- 不会因工作时造成的伤亡而被起诉 - 好吧
- for damages while they're on the job. - Okay.
但兴许我们可以把罪名改为疏忽致死
But maybe we can file a wrongful death.
- 我需要让罗宾的父母签字 - 休伊
- I just got to get Robin's parents to sign off on it. - Hughie,
- 过来陪我坐会 - 爸爸 我正在...
- come sit with me. - Dad, I'm right...
好吧
Okay.
好孩子
Good for you.
你想为罗宾声张正义
You want to make this right, what happened to Robin.
但你无能为力
But you can't.
签了它吧
So sign this.
什么
What?
这可是一大笔钱 休伊
This is a lot of money, Hughie.
我们需要这笔钱
We could really use it.
不行 爸爸 他们杀了她
I can't... dad, they killed her.
你现实点行不行
Be realistic, okay?
就算我们能付得起律师费...
Even if we could pay for a lawyer...
事实上我们不行 我们没法起诉
And that's a big if... There's no case.
她当时在街上
She was in the street.
就像公交车撞了她一样
Be like if a bus hit her.
爸爸 她离人行道只有一步之遥
Dad, she was one step off the curb.
- 我亲眼所见 - 休伊 听我说
- I saw it! - Hughie, look. Look.
- 你无能为力 - 为什么
- You can't do this. - Why not?
- 爸爸 我有... - 你没有斗志
- Dad, I have... - You don't have the fight.
从来都没有过
You never have.
对不起 但这是事实
I'm sorry, but it's-it's true.
我也一样
Neither do I.
现在
Now...
过来陪我坐会 好吗
Come and... come and sit with me, okay?
正在播《斯蒂尔传奇》呢
Remington Steele's on.
休伊 你去哪
Hughie! Where you going?
沃特总公司门外铺上了红地毯
The red carpet outside of Vought headquarters,
即将开始年度股东大会
here for the annual shareholders presentation...
她来了
There she is.
欢迎来到纽约
Welcome to New York.
我是艾希莉·巴雷特 人力资源总管
I'm Ashley Barrett, director of talent relations.
这些人都是为我而来吗
So, uh, are all these people here for me?
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
他们还能为谁而来呢
Who else would they be here for?
来吧
Come on.
我们要迟到了
We're running late.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
毫无疑问 如今是超级英雄产业的
it is without a doubt a good time
黄金时期
to be in the superhero business.
我们的净利润提高了百分之14
Our net income is up 14%.
我们最新的电影《G战警之世界大战》
Our latest film, G-men: World war,
在全球取得了
just grossed shy
17亿美元的票房
of $1.7 billion world-wide.
今年秋天 我们最新的主题公园
And this fall, we break ground
将在巴黎城郊破土动工
on our newest theme park outside of Paris.
本公司的品牌机遇数不胜数
The branding opportunities are limitless.
但是 你们知道 这些都不重要
But, you know, none of that really matters.
因为我们的主要工作是 管理 支持
Because job one is managing, supporting,
并给勇敢的英雄们提供建议
and advising the brave heroes
他们每天都置自身于险境中
who put themselves in harm's way each and every day
只为我们的安危
for us.
让我们来看看吧
Let's take a look.
一个没有犯罪的世界
A world without crime,
所有人尽享自由与正义
with liberty and justice for all,
多亏了沃特大家族的
that's within our reach,
200多名超级英雄
thanks to the 200-plus superheroes
让这一切都近在眼前
in the vought family.
我们能看见美好的未来
We see a bright future ahead,
现在每一个城镇里都有一个沃特公司的英雄
where there is a Vought hero in every town.
对了 迄今为止你表现很好
You're doing really well, by the way, so far.
可我还什么也没做
I-I haven't done anything yet.
正是如此 你在18岁到49岁的中西部居民及保守天主教徒中
Yeah, exactly. You're already up two-and-a-half points with midwesterners
支持率已经上升了2.5%
and conservative christians in 18 to 49.
顺便说一下 你试镜时讲的那段话
That speech, by the way, your audition...
很谦虚 很谦虚
It was modest... It was humble.
真是一个极其聪明的选择
Really fucking smart choice.
因为我是认真的
Uh, I-I meant it.
是的 这就是我们喜欢你的原因
Yeah, that's why we love you.
所以 你准备好改变你的生活了吗
So you ready for your life to change?
包括沃特公司
Including the jewel
王冠上的珍宝
in Vought's crown,
世上迄今为止最强大的
the greatest superhero team
超级英雄联盟
the world's ever seen:
七巨头
The Seven.
这是我们的职责 也是我们的荣誉
That is our job, our honor.
我们是沃特
We are Vought.
我们成就超级英雄
We make heroes super.
我有一个意外惊喜给大家
I have a very exciting surprise for you.
七巨头的一员
Both a member of the Seven,
也是七大洋之主
and lord of the seven seas,
亲自到场 有请深水主
live and in person, the Deep.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢大家
Thank you, everybody.
在作为七巨头
After a long,
荣耀征战许久之后
distinguished career with the Seven,
我的好朋友点灯侠退休了
my good friend, the Lamplighter, has retired.
让我们向他致以大大的感谢
Let's give him a big "Thank you."
你们觉得如何
What do you say?
谢谢你 点灯侠
Thank you, Lamplighter!
但现在
But now,
我们要展望未来
as we turn towards the future,
我想向你们介绍一位很特别的人
I'd like to introduce someone very special.
我个人已经迫不及待地想和她并肩作战了
And I, for one, can't wait to work with her.
让我们热烈欢迎星光
Please welcome Starlight.
上台吧 该你上了
Go. Go. That's you.
女士们 先生们 星光和深水主
Ladies and gentlemen, Starlight and the Deep.
星光 我爱你
I love you, Starlight!
我们爱你
We love you!
嘿 哥们 你还好吗
Hey, buddy, you okay?
嘿 哥们
Hey, buddy!
是不是酷毙了
Pretty cool, huh?
来 看看这个
Oh, hey, check this out.
我们在地心轨道上有两颗视界4号卫星
We have two World View-4 satellites in geocentric orbit.
我们能从600多公里高空读取逃逸车辆的车牌号
We can essentially read a getaway car's license plate from 380 miles up.
这真是...
That is just...
我是说...
I mean...
我天 我之前用的是从易贝买的警用扫描仪
G... I was working with a police scanner that I bought on ebay.
哈哈 你再也不需要用那个了
Yeah, well, not anymore you're not.
等你看完餐厅会更惊喜哦
Oh, and wait till you check out the dining room.
我们或许从格莱美西酒馆偷了米罗酒哦
We, uh, may or may not have stolen miro from Gramercy Tavern.
喝起来真他妈棒
Yeah, he's fan-fucking-tastic.
这个是他的 对吧
That's his, isn't it?
爱国者吗 是的
Homelander's? Yeah.
你也很快会有自己的座位
But you'll have your own soon.
来 过来
Here. Come on.
试一下吧
Give it a test drive.
来吧
Come on.
你还好吗
oh, you... you okay?
只是...
It's just...
我之前总是站在镜子前面
I used to stand in the mirror,
假装自己在这个地方
pretending to be where I am right now.
你知道吗
You know something?
我的第一天
On my first day, I, uh...
我感觉自己像个骗子
Well, I felt like a fraud.
是啊 但是好消息是大家都有同感
Yeah. But the good news is, everybody feels that way.
谢谢你
Thank you.
并且 我们是一个团队了
And, hey, we're a team now.
我们会互相帮助的
We'll help each other out.
我猜你从小就在墙上贴了一张爱国者的海报
I bet growing up you had a poster of Homelander on your wall, huh?
不 其实 我
No, actually, I...
我也说不清 爱国者他
I don't know, Homelander's so...
他就像耶稣一样
He's like Jesus or something.
说实话
If you want to know the truth,
我其实贴了一张你的海报
I actually had a poster of you.
真的吗
Really?
是的 我有点
Yeah. Yeah. I kind of...
我对你有种学生时代的迷恋感
I kind of had a schoolgirl crush on you.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
我希望说出来你不会觉得太唐突
I hope that's not inappropriate to say.
不不不 这一点也不唐突
No, no, no, no, no. It's not inappropriate at all.
就是 就是有点疯狂
It's just, it's kind of wild.
怎么了
What?
你刚说的 你之前很迷恋我
I mean, you said you had a crush on me.
我就觉得 你懂的...
I figured that, you know...
- 这真是... - 等下 别走啊
- That is... - Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey.
听着 你很漂亮
Look, you're gorgeous.
我不是说 我不是说要滚床单
I'm not... I'm not talking about sex,
就来点口交就行
just a little bit of pole-smoking.
等下 等下 别走
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, wait, wait.
这只是测试下你有多想成为七巨头的一员
It's just a question of how bad you want to be in the Seven.
你说什么
Excuse me?
别激动啊
Take it easy.
冷静一下 我们只是在聊天而已
Settle down. We're just, we're just talking.
听着 我知道你很强大
And look, I know that you're powerful.
我明白 你的超能力可不是盖的
I get it. Your powers are no joke.
问题是
The thing is...
我是这里的二把手
I am number two around here.
所以 如果我发话
So, like, if I say so,
你知道 你就会被赶出这里
you know, you'd be out of here.
尤其是在你袭击我之后
Especially since you attacked me.
我什么
I what?
是啊 比如说
Yeah. Look.
爱荷华州的甜心 得梅因州的守护者
I mean, Lowa's sweetheart, the defender of Des Moines,
精神错乱 袭击了深水主
just went psycho on the Deep.
我是说 这
I mean, that...
这能让你从这一行消失的
that could put you out of the business.
是啊
Yeah.
尾巴夹在两腿中间 哭哭啼啼回家找妈妈
I mean, home to mommy, tail tucked between your legs.
想想所有那些孩子们
Just think of all those kids.
我指那些
I mean, the kids.
那些崇拜你的孩子们
Those kids who look up to you,
他们会悲痛欲绝的
they'd just be shattered.
那并不是你真正想要的 对吧
I mean, that's not what you really want, right?
或者我们可以组成团队
Or we come together as a team.
咱俩 你就忍一下
You and me, we just roll with the punches,
也就忍个三分钟吧
for, like, three minutes, maybe.
没什么大不了的
It's not a big deal.
然后你知道会发生什么吗
And then you know what happens?
你的所有梦想都会成真
All your dreams come true.
我肯定你们全都听说了
I'm sure you guys have all heard
隐形人昨天晚上在杨克斯
that Translucent stopped a home invasion
阻止了一场入室盗窃 保护了一个年轻的单亲妈妈
in Yonkers last night, a young, single mother
和她的两个孩子 真是不可思议
and her two kids. Just incredible. Just...
告诉我们 你怎么能够隐形的
So tell us, how are you able to... to vanish?
不 我并不是真正隐形
No, I don't actually vanish.
我的皮肤可以变成一种能弯曲光线的碳素超材料
My skin turns into this carbon meta-material that bends the light.
就像隐形斗篷一样
Like an invisibility cloak.
好的 但是我们要问清楚
All right, but just to be clear,
你必须全裸 对吗
you have to be completely naked, right?
感谢你来上节目 老兄 爱你哦
I appreciate you coming on the show, my man. I love you.
各位尽请期待《隐形特工队2》
You guys stay tuned for a behind-the-scenes look
幕后花絮 稍后 隐形人本人将...
at Invisible Force 2, and later, Translucent himself...
你对保姆监控摄像头感兴趣吗
You interested in a nanny cam?
因为我们正好在搞特价
'Cause we're actually running a special on that.
这只熊挺畅销的
Um, it's a pretty popular bear.
它眼睛里有摄像头
There's cameras in the eyes.
告诉我
Tell me,
有多少保姆会这样摇晃孩子
how many nannies shake their babies?
什么
Uh, I'm sorry?
狠狠地摇 就像
You know, a good... hard shake, like...
就像把番茄酱从瓶子里倒出来一样
Like tryin' to get ketchup out of a bottle.
百分之一 或者更少
One percent? Less?
我不太清楚
I-I don't really know.
真有趣
Funny, that.
这破玩意在全球卖了十亿美元
They sell a billion dollars worth of that shit worldwide.
这就说明问题了 不是吗
Goes to show you, doesn't it?
只要能把人们吓唬住
The bollocks people will believe
他们就会相信你的这些屁话
if you get them scared enough.
是吧
Cool.
没错
Cool, cool.
有什么我能为您效劳的
Is there anything I can help you with today, or...?
我就不跟你浪费时间了 休伊
I'm not gonna piss you about, Hughie.
我听说了罗宾的事
I heard what happened to Robin.
不好意思 你是谁
I'm... I'm... I'm sorry, who are you?
她当时没有站在马路上
She wasn't in the street.
她只跨出了马路牙子一步
She was one step off the fucking curb.
而且你没收那笔赔偿
And you didn't take the pay-off.
没错 我在问你你到底是谁
Yeah. I said, who the hell are you?
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我叫布彻
My name's Butcher.
比利·布彻
Billy Butcher.
听着 我想着
Listen, I was thinking that, uh,
咱俩该好好聊聊
you and me should have a little bit of a chat.
你是联邦调查局的探员吗
Y-you're a fed?
你的口音可不太像
You don't sound like a fed.
怎么 探员就不能是移民吗
What, I can't immigrate?
海港里那位浑身绿色的大姐
There's a giant green slapper with her ass in the harbor
可不这么想
that says different.
但是你看起来也不像
You don't really look like one, either.
是吗 我看起来像啥
No? What do I look like?
像色情版《黑客帝国》的主演
Like you're starring in a porn version of The Matrix.
证件上白纸黑字写着呢
Well, it's all right there in black and white.
好吧 那我能帮你做些什么
Okay. Uh, what exactly can I do for you?
不 你会错意了 休伊
No, you got it all wrong, Hughie.
应该说我能为你做什么
It's what I can do for you.
你不是一个人 孩子
You see, you ain't alone, son.
你不知道 这种事发生过太多次了
It happens a lot more than you think.
超级英雄每年都要间接害死上百的人
Supes lose hundreds of people each year to collateral damage.
怎么可能 那早该上新闻了
No. Come on, that'd be all over the news.
人人都会伸冤讨伐
People would be screaming bloody murder.
有时候是会有报道
Yeah, look, there might be the odd mention of it
像罗宾这件事
now and again, like with Robin,
但更多的事件
but there's a fuck-sight more that happens
就这样被隐瞒了
that just gets swept right under the rug.
为什么
Why?
还不够明显吗
Ain't it obvious?
为了电影票 周边产品
Movie tickets, merchandising,
主题公园 电子游戏
theme parks, video games.
这项数十亿美元的全球产业
A multi-billion dollar global industry
得到了企业说客
supported by corporate lobbyists
和两党政客的共同支持
and politicians on both sides.
但你之所以没有听说这些事件
But the main reason that you won't hear about it
是因为公众不想去了解这些事实
is 'cause the public don't want to know about it.
人们依赖于超级英雄带给他们的安全感
See, people love that cozy feeling that supes give them.
一群自命不凡的混蛋
Some golden cunt
从天而降 拯救世界
swoop out of the sky and save the day
这样你完全不用自己动手了
so you don't got to do it yourself.
但你如果知道一半他们干的那些勾当
But if you knew half the shit they get up to...
人神共愤啊
Fuckin' diabolical.
这时候 就需要我出手了
But then... That's where I come in.
出手做什么
Come in to... to do what?
在这群混蛋越界时惩罚他们
Spank the bastards when they get out of line.
你要怎么惩罚超级英雄
How do you spank a supe?
跟我来 孩子
Come on, son.
去哪里
Uh, where?
你会喜欢的
You'll love it.
不太可能 听着
Uh, not likely. Uh, listen.
我觉得差不多了 我不太想参与
I think this is good, I'm good.
谢谢你这番诡异至极的谈话
Uh, thank you for an extremely weird conversation,
但我不想跟你去下个地方了
but, uh, I don't want to go to a second location with you.
我现在要回去上班了
So, I'm gonna get back to work.
谢谢你
Thank you.
休伊 休伊
Hughie! Hughie.
这是你唯一的机会 兄弟
This is your one and only, mate.
我走了就不会回来了
Once I go, I'm gone.
我在给你提供一个
I'm offering you the opportunity
替你女朋友报仇的机会
to get them that got your girl.
你还怕失去什么呢
What have you got to lose
你已经一无所有了
that you ain't already lost?
这是哪里
Where are we?
别说话
Keep your mouth shut.
哈里
Harry.
收到你的信息了
Got your message.
谢谢你这名遵纪守法的好市民
Thank you for being an upstanding citizen.
你这是警察暴行 兄弟
You know this is fucking police brutality, man.
如果我给你开门被发现了
You know what they'll do to me,
你知道他们会怎么惩罚我吗
they catch me letting you in?
如果你不开门 我会加倍惩罚你
Not half of what I'll do if you don't.
他刚刚说你是警察
Did he just say you were police?
警察和探员对这些混蛋来说都一样
Yeah, you know, cop, fed, all the same to twats like that.
老天爷耶
Holy shit.
把你惊掉的下巴安回去
Pick your jaw up off the floor
试着合群点
and try to blend in.
这是唯一一个
This is the only place
能让超人英雄满足自己见不得人的小癖好
where the supes can scratch their filthy little itch
又不被狗仔拍到的地方
without the paps taking snaps.
等等 那是以西结
Wait, wait, wait. That's Ezekiel.
那个穿基督披风的家伙
The "Capes for Christ" Guy...
总是在宣扬
preaches all that...
"同性恋都该去死"
"Pray the gay away" shit.
然而他现在搂着两个男人
And now he's the meat in the manwich.
该死的伪君子
Fucking hypocrite.
继续放
Keep going forward.
对了 继续
That's it. Further.
继续
Further.
就是这
There. There.
- 停 - 等等
- Stop. - Wait, wait, wait.
火车头 火车头现在在这吗
A-train's... A-train's here right now?
之前在 这是昨晚的录像
Was. This is from last night.
音量开大
Turn it up.
不敢相信你把一个婊子撞成了肉酱
I cannot believe you ran through a bitch.
想听件更不可思议的事吗
You want to hear something crazy?
我撞到她的时候跑的太快
I ran so fast through this bitch
不小心吞下了她一颗臼齿
that I swallowed one of her molars.
就像在高速公路上吃了只虫子
Like a bug on the fucking freeway.
老兄 这太恶心了
Dude, that's nasty.
他们在笑
They're laughing.
就像 她只是个笑话
Just... like she's a joke.
他们他妈的在笑
They're fucking laughing.
那你打算怎么做
So what are you gonna do about it?
我的天
Oh, for chrissakes.
把自己拾掇干净
Clean yourself up.
别让他们看见你这副样子
Never let them see you like this.
隐形人 你他妈就是个变态
Translucent, you're a goddamn pervert.
我马上就走
I'll just go.
他们都这副德行吗
They're all like that?
全都是吗 爱国者也是吗
All of them? Even Homelander?
爱国者是例外
Homelander's the exception.
他烟酒不沾
He doesn't drink, doesn't smoke.
那家伙是个圣人
Man's a Saint.
但剩下的 都是
But the rest of 'em, yeah.
原谅我爆粗 操他妈的混蛋们
Pardon my French, fuck those fuckers.
给你
Here.
看看这个
Have a shufti of that.
- 这些是什么 - 这是罗宾遇害那天的
- What are these? - That's the police log
警方日志
the day that Robin got murdered.
几场酒吧斗殴 几辆车被偷了
Couple of bar fights. A few cars got nicked.
但你知道里面缺了什么吗
But you know what's not in there?
没有银行警报被触发
No bank alarms going off.
中央拘留所里没有人被起诉
No one charged at Central Booking.
火车头才没有阻止那两个银行劫匪
A-train stopped two bank robbers, my arse.
妈的肯定有人在隐瞒什么东西
Someone's fucking hiding something.
- 隐瞒什么 - 我也不知道
- Hiding what? - Well, I don't know,
也许就是他那晚干了什么破事
whatever dodgy shit he was up to that night.
为什么他不停下来 那袋子里究竟有什么东西
Why couldn't he stop? I mean, what was in that bag?
他在躲谁
You know? Who was he running from?
- 又或者说他要跑到哪里去 - 没错
- Or where was he running to? - Bingo.
搞清楚这个 那傻逼就完蛋了 相信我
Work that out, and we'll have the fucker, I can smell it.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 那...
Okay, so, um...
我能帮上什么忙吗
What can I do to help?
下面这些就是你要做的
Here's what you do.
打电话告诉沃特你会拿钱 然后把保密协议签了
Ring vought, tell 'em you'll take the money, sign the nda,
但条件是签协议的时候 火车头得在场
but only if A-train's there in person when you do it.
为什么他一定要在场
Why does A-train need to be there?
然后他们就会带你过安检
Then they'll take you into the Seven Tower,
进入七雄塔
through security, mate,
- 然后你得去装个窃听器 - 窃听器
- and then you're gonna plant a bug. - A bug?
对 这样我们才能听到他们讲什么
A bug. And we'll have a little listen.
然后就能弄清楚他们在搞什么鬼
See what's really going on.
好吧... 不好意思 先让我捋清楚
Okay, let me just... sorry, let me just get this straight.
你要我... 你要我自己去七雄塔
You want me to... you want me to go to Seven Tower by myself,
然后还要我去装个窃听器
and-and you want me to plant a bug,
就像... 就他妈像007一样
like I'm... what, like I'm fuckin' James Bond?
- 对没错 是这样 - 你是联邦调查局的
- Yeah, exactly. You got it. - You're FBI.
这样的话 为什么你不搞个搜查令
If you're FBI, then get a warrant.
为什么... 你还会需要我
Why do you... why do you even need me?
听好了 休伊 就算我有搜查令
Hughie, Hughie, look, mate, I got a warrant, all right?
但那个地方铜墙铁壁 根本无处下手
But that place is firewalled, untappable,
锁的比修女的贴身裤还要紧
and locked up tighter than a nun's knickers.
我这辈子都不可能进得去
I couldn't get myself in there in a million years.
但孩子 你可以进去
But you, son, you could do it.
- 不 我不行 - 你可以的
- No, no, I can't, okay? - Yeah.
我不行 你没看到火车头...
I can't. No. You didn't see A-train covered in...
然后我怎么样 我就应该进去
And-and I'm, what, I'm just supposed to go in there,
然后我... 我还要去和他握个手
and I'm supposed to... I'm supposed to shake his hand?
- 还得面带笑容吗 - 没错
- and smile? - Yeah.
我才不... 你知道我最喜欢的音乐家是谁吗
I'm not... do you know who my favorite musician is?
- 谁 - 詹姆斯·泰勒
- Who? - James Taylor.
第二个是西蒙和加芬克尔 第三个是比利·乔
Number two, Simon & Garfunkel. Number three, Billy Joel.
他们中没有一个会秘密潜入的
Any of those guys, they don't infiltrate.
明白吗 我不擅长偷偷潜入
Okay? I'm not an infiltrator.
休伊 休伊 你他妈像个男人好吗
Hughie, Hughie, fucking grow a pair.
你听到那混蛋是怎么嘲笑你女朋友的
You heard that cunt laughing at your girl.
不 不行
No. No. No.
不 我做不到
No, I can't. I can't do that.
很抱歉 我肯定会把这事搞砸的
I'm sorry, I'm just gonna fuck it up,
然后了你也装不了窃听器
and you're not gonna have your bug...
而且我会死的
And I'll be dead.
我... 我和你不一样
I'm not... I'm not like you.
真是太棒了 马德琳
This is amazing, Madelyn.
谢谢你 我家孩子拿到后一定会很高兴的
Thank you for this. My kid is gonna lose his mind.
区区小事 何足挂齿
Ah, it is our pleasure.
别拿到网上去卖就好了
Just do not sell it online.
好吧 你有什么想法
All right. What are you thinking?
巴尔的摩是座美丽的城市
Baltimore is a beautiful town.
但问题是
But you've got a problem.
你们的凶杀率上升到多少来着 62%吧
Your homicide rates are up, what, 62%?
很多案子警方都没办法结
The police are not closing cases.
你们都快要动用联邦生命线来渡过难关了
You're on the verge of needing a federal lifeline.
有话直说 马德琳
Cut to the chase, Madelyn.
你有什么人选可推荐
Who are you proposing?
努比亚王子
Nubian Prince.
对于你们的人口组成来说 他很合适
Fits your population's demo,
而且又不会太好战
but not too militant.
白种人也喜欢他
Caucasians love him, too, with a...
对他的支持率高达59%
59% approval rate.
我愿意跟你签一份三年的独家合同
I am willing to give you a three-year exclusive contract
包括全方位的公关支持
with full PR support,
而且周边产品的销售所得
and I'm gonna give you nine and a half points
我还会分给你们9.5个点
of the merchandising.
我还以为他在底特律
I thought he was in Detroit.
我们正在考虑人员调动
Well, we're thinking about making a move.
价格多少
How much?
一年三亿美元
$300 million a year.
我知道 你觉得这价格难以接受
I know, I know, it's a tough swallow.
但你我都心知肚明 你的城市需要一位英雄
But we both know that your city needs a hero.
一年两亿美元我就定下努比亚王子
$200 million for Nubian Prince.
这样民众也好接受
I can sell that.
抱歉 史蒂夫 这我没法接受
I'm sorry, Steve, I can't do it.
亚特兰大还等着呢
We've got Atlanta waiting in the wings.
我觉得你可以接受的
I think maybe you can.
此话怎讲
And why is that?
我碰巧知道了"化合物V"的事情
I happen to know about compound v.
"化合物V"是什么
What is compound v?
这东西能把你那些英雄的名声
It's the type of rumor that could really tarnish
都给败坏了
those heroes of yours.
没人想让这种事发生
Nobody wants that.
人们需要英雄
People need heroes.
我可以保证这事只会是谣言
Now, I can make sure that that stays a rumor,
因为我是你的朋友
because I'm a friend.
但友谊也是双刃剑
But friendship does cut both ways.
很抱歉 史蒂夫 我不知道你在讲什么
I'm sorry, Steve, I don't know what you're talking about.
一口价三亿美元
$300 million is the price,
不然我们就去找亚特兰大了
or we go to Atlanta.
所以 那有多棒
So, how amazing is it?
爱国者人怎么样
What's Homelander like?
他很忙 我还没有见到他 但...
He's busy. I haven't really met him yet, but...
妈 我得告诉你发生了什么
Mom, I got to tell you what happened.
我差点忘了
Oh, I forgot.
我和帕蒂还有翠西一起打麻将的时候
I was playing mah-jongg with Patty and Trish,
帕蒂一遍又一遍地讲她女儿怎样
and Patty is going on and on about how her daughter
考进医学院 我就想 那又怎么样
got into med school, and I'm thinking, so what?
我女儿还是七位超级英雄中的一员呢
My daughter got into the seven!
好吧 刚刚你想跟我讲什么来着
Anyway, so-so, what did you want to tell me?
一切都很好
Everything's great.
和我们梦想中的一切一样
Just how we dreamed.
妈妈 我得挂了
Mom, actually, you know what? I have to go.
那好吧 再见 亲爱的
All right. Bye, honey.
不好意思
Excuse me.
抱歉 你还好吗
I'm sorry, a-are you okay?
刚刚那通电话听起来...
Just seemed like a...
蛮难受的
tough call.
对不起 我不是有意要打扰你的
Sorry. I don't mean to bother you.
不 没事
No, no, it's okay.
我很好 只是...
I'm fine. I'm just...
只是今天过得有点糟糕而已
I'm just having a bad day.
是啊 我也是
Yeah, me, too.
那个... 是工作上的事吗 还是说...
Is it, like, a-a work thing, or...
是生活上的事吗
a-a life thing?
工作上的事情
It's a work thing.
你呢
You?
生活上的琐事
Life thing.
你知道怎么才会...
You know how you have this...
对自己有这样的认识吗
image of yourself?
就像 我以前觉得我自己很强大
Like, I thought I was strong.
就像有钢铁之躯一样
You know? Like, made of steel.
全然是一个斗士
A fighter.
然后...
And...
然后我就陷入了一种很可怕的情况
Then I was faced with this horrible situation
遇到了一个混蛋
with this asshole...
然后...
And...
我便在脑海中听到我妈妈对我说
I just heard my mom's voice in my head,
"保持微笑
"Keep smiling,
一切还要继续"
the show must go on,"
然后... 这次我丧失斗志了
and... I didn't fight.
我现在觉得很不舒服
And now I just feel sick.
某种程度上 是因为我干了那种事... 但是
Partly because I did it, but...
最主要是因为
Mostly because...
原来我并非自己所设想的那种人
Turns out I'm not who I thought I was.
很抱歉
Oh. Oh, I'm, um, sorry.
我... 我不是有意要把所有的事情
I-I didn't mean to just dump all of that
- 都向你倾诉的 - 不 不 没关系
- onto you. - No, no, it's totally fine that you dumped. Um...
你喜欢自己的工作吗
Listen, d-do you like your job?
我这辈子就只想要这个了
It's the only thing I've ever wanted.
那就是一份好工作了
And it's a good job?
你不是给小孩卖毒品的吧
Like, you're not selling kids smack?
没有 是一份好差事
No, it's a great job.
我可以帮助好多人
I could help a lot of people.
事情是这样的 我
Thing is, I, um...
以前认识这么一个女孩
used to know this girl,
我们常常一起去洛克菲勒大厦溜冰
and we used to go skating at Rockefeller,
我总是在一旁
and I'd be on the side
死死地抓住扶手
with this death grip on the rails.
而她会一头冲进溜冰场中间
She would just charge headfirst into the middle of the rink.
但她又不是 很厉害
And she wasn't... good.
她无数次地
Like, she fell...
摔倒
a lot...
可她却从不害怕
But she was never scared.
她总是说
And she always used to say:
"即使你摔了个狗吃屎 也不代表
"Just 'cause you fall on your ass
你就站不起来了"
doesn't mean you have to stay there."
你只是摔了次狗吃屎罢了
So you fell on your ass, you know?
又并不能说明你是谁
That's not who you are.
所以你想好你是谁了吗
So who are you?
我是个斗士
I'm a fighter.
我会战斗到底
I'm gonna fight.
嗯
Yeah.
我会把那个畜生的头
I'm gonna take that son of a bitch's head
- 从身上拧下来 - 哇 那可太
- clean off his body. - Okay. Wow, that was...
好吧
Okay.
很酷
Cool.
有点瘆人 但是
Little scary, but...
但 但很酷
but-but cool.
对了 我叫休伊
I'm-I'm hughie, by the way.
我是安妮
Annie.
好吧 兄弟 我同意
Okay, man. I'm in.
好了 接通了
Okay, it's ringing.
喂
Yeah, hello?
你好
Hi. Hi.
你好 你好 弗德曼先生
Yes, hello. Hello, Mr. Friedman.
我是休伊·坎波 我收到了你的信息
It's hughie Campbell. I got your message,
还有 还有那四万五的钱 这
and-and $45k, it's just...
救命钱 太及时了
it's just... it's bingo, like, life-changing.
但在我签字之前还有一个附加条件
but I just need one thing before I-I sign anything.
我需要一个道歉
I need an apology
- 火车头的道歉 - 但他已经致歉了
- from A-train. - Uh, he already apologized.
哦 不 不 不
Well, no, no, no.
他没有 当然 他表达了
No, he hasn't. Yes, he sent his...
他表达了他的忏悔和同情
he sent his regrets and his sympathies on...
在电视上 但我
on TV, but I-I...
我要是能得到他一个当面的道歉的话
if I could just get an apology face-to-face,
就最好了
that would be fantastic.
就是为了结束
Just to... just for closure,
让我彻底放下这件事
just to put... just to put a b-button on it.
我知道了 但是 但
Okay, yeah. But, uh...
休伊 实话跟你说 这恐怕做不到
Hugh, I'm telling you, the answer's gonna be no.
好吧 那 那如果这样的话
All right, in that... in that case,
你可以给我 喂
can you just give me... uh, hello?
我觉得 他好像挂了
I think... they hung up.
我觉得他们不会答应
I don't think they're gonna go for it.
不 他们会答应的
Oh, yes, they will.
星光
Starlight.
你可不想在第一次正式会议就迟到吧
Don't want to be late to your first official meeting.
我准备了一整套欢迎辞呢
I had a whole welcome speech planned.
抱歉 队长
Sorry, sir.
入座吧 叫我爱国者就好了
Please, Homelander's fine.
我都开始寻思你到底会不会来了
Beginning to wonder if you'd even show up.
意思是 毕竟那么大的压力
I mean, all that pressure,
任何人都会有点难承受
it's a lot for anyone to swallow.
是呀 别担心 我很好
Yeah. Don't worry, I'll be fine.
这不来了吗
I'm here,
而且我也不会走
and I'm not going anywhere.
回到正题 好吗
Can we get back to this, please?
这是很严重的罪行 这群混蛋在我的电影
This is a serious crime. These assholes pirated my movie
发行三周前就出了盗版
three weeks before release,
你一走上第五大街
and you can't walk down 5th Avenue
就能看到一堆无牌爱国者T恤
without bumping into a table of unlicensed Homelander shirts.
每年在版权侵犯上沃特都要花费
Copyright infringement is costing Vought
12亿美元
$1.2 billion per year.
这都是我们口袋里抠走的钱
That's money out of our pockets.
我们每个人都要摊个四亿吧
We've all got, what, four points each?
这他妈
What the fuck?
原来你有四亿块啊
You got four points?
明显人家律师也更牛
And clearly better lawyers.
大家伙 消停消停
Hey, hey, hey, guys, come on.
够了
Stop.
星光会怎么看我们
What's Starlight gonna think?
听着我们为了些小钱吵架
Listening to us haggling over nickels.
我的天 我们可是七巨头
We're the Seven, for god's sake.
对内也拿出点巨头的样子
Whether we're out there or we're in here.
好了 我现在想听听
Now, what I do want to hear
你们这周都救了什么人
is who you saved this week.
嗯
Huh?
谁赞成这个想法
Who's up for that?
玄色
Black Noir.
从你开始吧 老兄
Let's start with you, man.
你养狗吗
Do you have a dog?
并不
No.
好了 把你的手机给我
All right, give us your phone.
还有一群操蛋的安保要糊弄
There's fuck-all security to worry about.
他们也就一群蠢货而已
In fact, they're a bunch of muppets.
金属探测器检测不出这个
And the metal detector won't pick this up.
懂吗 他们大概会先带你过安检
Right? And what they'll probably do is take you
然后再去会议室
through the security and then up into the boardroom.
你坐下来 脸色好点 说话好听点
Sit down. Be nice, congenial.
然后非常礼貌地跟他们讲 你要去拉泡屎
Then, real polite-like, tell 'em you're gonna take a fake shit.
走进厕所隔间 拿出窃听器
Go into the bog, take the bug out.
把塑料外壳撕下来 露出有粘性的一端
Peel back the plastic bit to reveal the sticky side.
再把塑料壳扔到厕所里 冲掉
Put the plastic bit in the bog. Flush it.
回到会议室
Then go back into the boardroom,
坐下来 露出大大的微笑
sit down... big smiles...
把窃听器安在桌子下面
plant the bug underneath the table.
易如反掌 手到擒来
Easy peasy japanesey.
就这么简单 就是这样
Bob's your uncle. That's that.
还就这样
That's that?
这这这 也太复杂了吧
That was... that was a lot.
这 我 等等 你能 能再重复一遍吗
Th... I've... hold on, can you just... can you repeat it again?
- 再慢一点行吗 因为 我 - 嘘
- Just a little bit slower? Because I... - Shh.
听着
Listen.
- 操 - 休伊 冷静一点 好吗
- Fuck. - Hughie, calm down, all right?
这就像《黑客帝国》里的那个场景
This is like that scene in the matrix.
现在 你可以选择那颗红色药丸 明白吗
Now, you could take the fucking red pill, right?
然后下半生就打打飞机
Spend the rest of your life jacking off,
喝点小茶 流点小泪
crying into your chai tea green latte,
诸如此类 或者
what the fuck. Or...
你大可以选择那颗蓝色的药丸
You could take the blue pill.
等等我是不是说反颜色了 不管怎样 选另一颗
Or is it the red pill? Anyway, take the other pill
别他妈婆婆妈妈了
and quit being a cunt.
你想让我选哪颗
Which pill do you want me to take?
别婆婆妈妈就行
Just quit being a cunt.
我就想说这个
That's what I'm saying.
操 好吧
Fuck me. Okay.
先生 请把口袋里的东西拿出来 好吗
Sir, could you empty your pockets, please?
谢谢合作
Thank you.
抱歉 请 请问 我
Excuse me, can-can I, uh...
我可以去趟卫生间吗
Can I use your bathroom?
话先说在前头 火车头的道歉
Just to be clear, A-train's apology
并不代表他承认任何形式的罪责
isn't an admission of any sort of culpability whatsoever.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
我对你女朋友身上发生的事儿感到很抱歉
I'm sorry about what happened to your girlfriend,
好吗
all right?
兄弟 你还好吗
Hey, dude, are you okay?
没事
Fine.
我接受你的道歉
I appreciate the apology.
世事无常 对吧
Accidents happen, right?
毕竟
After all,
你当时是在忙着拯救世界
I mean, you were saving the world.
那太好了 非常感谢 正如你所知
Okay, great. Thank you so much. As you know,
打击犯罪 永远在路上啊
a crimefighter's work is never done.
道格拉斯会继续处理剩下的文书工作 好吗
Douglas here will handle the rest of the paperwork for you, okay?
谢谢了
Thank you.
我能上个厕所吗
Can I use your bathroom?
我去
What the fuck?
我就那么直直地看着他的眼睛 然后微笑
And I look him right in the eye, and I smile.
太爽了 兄弟
And that was awesome, man,
能跟他面对面瞪死他
just getting to stare that asshole down.
我知道你干这行的理由了
I get why you dig this job.
就是因为有些小瞬间是吧
Yeah, you know, it has its moments, doesn't it?
你是对的 去他妈的火车头
You were right. Fuck a-train.
去你的火车头 去你的七巨头
Fuck a-train. Fuck-fuck the seven.
去他妈的... 七巨头
Fuck all... Seven.
我们在...
What are we, uh...
我们在这干嘛呢
What are we doing here?
你要去上班了吧 不是吗
Well, you got to go to work, don't you?
是啊 但我不用...
Yeah, but, um, I don't, uh...
我的意思是 这就是我所需要的全部了 好吗
Well, I mean, that's all I need you for right now, yeah?
我知道 我的意思是 但我可以...
Yeah, I mean, but I-I can...
我可以帮忙解决其他的问题 你知道吗
I can help with other stuff, you know?
我可以... 我可以做你的技术支持
I could... I could be, like, your tech guy.
你知道吗 我可以在卡车里戴着对讲机
You know? Like, I could be in the Van with the thing
然后 就说类似"他在左边的大厅"
and, like, you know, "He's down the hall to the left."
就像 我可以...
Like, I can...
是啊 听着 孩子 我...
Yeah, look, son, I, uh...
我觉得最好我就此接手吧
I think it's best that I take it from here.
- 你懂意思吧 - 是的 但是我可以...
- You know what I mean? - Yeah, but I-I can...
我真的能帮你
I can really help.
我知道你能帮我 我知道了
I know you can help. I got it.
等等...
Oh, w... oh, hey, wait.
你有没有见过一个混蛋撕掉四万五千美元
You ever see an asshole tear up $45k?
休伊
Hughie.
你是个好孩子
You're a good lad.
斯蒂尔威尔女士 我不确定你会打电话
Ms. Stillwell, I wasn't sure you'd call.
你居然还生气 但是 我可以...
This fucking chafes, but, um...
我愿意为努比亚王子降价到二点三亿美元
I'm willing to come down to $230 million for nubian prince.
这很合理 玛迪 谢谢你
That's very reasonable, Maddie. Thank you.
史蒂夫 还有关于这个化合物V
And, Steve, this, um, compound v,
以及你听说的有关我的英雄们的传言
any rumors you may have heard about my heroes...
都是诽谤而且完全不真实
Libelous and completely untrue.
但我们都知道流言是怎么传出去的
But we all know how rumors spread,
所以... 我劝你谨言慎行
so... I'd appreciate your discretion.
当然
Of course.
我保证
You have my word.
谢谢你
Thank you.
一路平安
Have a safe flight home.
法治化本身是个十分棘手的问题了
Policing cities is a thorny enough issue as it is,
我们还要允许超级英雄进入国防吗
but allowing superheroes into national defense?
这跟战争私有化有什么区别
We'd basically be privatizing war.
晚安 休伊
Good night, hughie.
你要锁门了吗
You'll lock up?
- 是的 - 好的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
谢谢 盖里
Thanks, Gary.
抱歉 我们要关门了
Sorry, we're closing up.
有人吗
Hello?
你是谁
Who are you?
混蛋
The fuck?
就在你面前啊 二逼
Right in front of you, prick.
你觉得我找不到这个吗
You think I wouldn't find this thing?
休伊
Hughie.
你个蠢球 我从七雄塔跟踪你到这
You pussy, I followed you from the fucking tower.
不要 不要 不要
No, no, no!
车里那个和你一起的人是谁
Who's that guy you were with, in the car?
- 他是谁 - 我不知道...
- Who was he? - I don't...
- 他让你做这些的吗 - 我不知道
- He put you up to this? - I don't know!
他只是个滴滴车司机 好吗
He was just some uber driver, okay?
别跟我瞎扯 还滴滴车司机
Don't give me some bullshit! Uber driver!
你当我傻逼吗
Do you think I'm a fucking idiot?
- 你为什么装这个窃听器 - 求你了
- Why'd you plant the bug? - Please.
求你了 求你了 求你了
Please, please, please.
不要 求你了
No, please.
我们是七巨头
We're the seven,
地球上最强大
earth's most mighty,
最无私的
champions of the innocent,
操他妈的傻逼
motherfucker!
抱歉把你的店砸了
Sorry about the mess.
你最好赶紧滚 休伊
You should fuck off, hughie.
休伊 快跑
Hughie, run!
好啊 好啊 好啊
Well, well, well,
如果不是这个看不见的混蛋
if it ain't the invisible cunt.
你在这啊
There you are.
所以你是谁
So who are you?
该死的间谍吗
Fucking spy?
谁的间谍
For who? Huh?
你他妈告诉我
You're gonna fucking tell me,
不然他妈脑壳给你敲碎
or I'm gonna smash your fucking scalp off!
你他妈到底是谁
Who the fuck are you?
我只能告诉你你是谁
I'll tell you who you are.
你就是个傻逼
A fucking moron.
"隐形人"除了"看不见"
"Translucent" doesn't even mean "Invisible."
还意味着"半导电"
It means "Semi-transparent."
他死了吗
Is he... is he dead?
他是...
Is he...
反正动是不动了
Well, he ain't moving.
卧槽 妈的
Oh, fuck. Oh, shit.
你怎么知道能电死他
How'd you know the electric could do the job?
皮肤中的碳
Skin's carbon.
有高导电性
Highly conductive.
我在肥伦秀上看的
Saw it on, uh, Jimmy Fallon.
我可能永远都想不到这个
Would've taken me forever to work that one out.
干得好
Good job.
我们把他给扔了
Let's get him in the boot.
等等 等等 你说什么
Wait, wait, what? Wait, what? What?
扔进后备箱
The trunk.
不不 我是说 我们要... 我们要...
No, no, I mean, what are we... what are we...
我们要拿他怎么办
what are we doing with him?
休伊 你刚刚杀了七巨头中的一个
Well, hughie, you just offed one of the seven, mate.
我吗 我...
Me? I...
是你开着那该死的车撞了他
you-you hit him with a fucking car!
是你是我重要吗
Look, potato, fucking po-tah-to.
反正我们俩现在都惹上事了
We're both in a shitload of trouble.
不不不 我们没有 这只是...
No, no, no, we're not! It's... it...
是他来攻击的我们
He-he attacked us, okay?
然后你不还是个警察吗
And you're-you're a federal officer, you know?
赶紧他妈的给联邦调查局打电话啊
Just-just call the fucking FBI.
好吧 好吧 听着
Yeah, o-okay, so, look,
事实上 我不是警察
technically, I'm not a fed.
你说什么
What?
那你他妈是谁
Then who the fuck are you?
别担心 小伙计 只是个小颠簸
Don't worry about it, kiddo. It's just a little turbulence.
会没事的
It'll be okay.
爸爸 爸爸 爸爸
Dad. Dad. Dad!
他在这干什么
What's he doing out here?
你们是朋友吗
Are you guys friends?
我的天
oh, my god.